{
    "id": "0c2cada2c5214043840c6904ab5eaf6b",
    "title": "Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Maria bought some flowers which she wanted to give her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6b43f81ba2e4647af79197543b92415"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know the reason why she hates me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c86e74d1a3294b849fdf583fbdd2b66d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He drove fast so that he might reach the airport in time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6733f3fff5884dcaa08762167d1cbb76"
        },
        {
            "question": "The professor was speaking so softly that we could not hear him at all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6a02df6c7104bf981dcae891df47a04"
        },
        {
            "question": "The gardener said that all the plants had been pruned neatly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44dcb95529054aad8c2a32b74192df9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The angler said that he hadn’t caught any fish that morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b6c166e69f7420a806dfd7f8a75a43c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wondered if she was free.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3890737cc6ef4c348164a1fae0d86480"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though he didn’t receive formal schooling, he is clever and industrious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4b9013590a184307950edd6b5f635333"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys who misbehaved in the class were suspended.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc2551b8fde6445c8a7004d98d861d9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He who laughs last laughs best.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Adjective clause",
                "Adverb clause",
                "Noun clause"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0c6f7eabaec742a5affc017fca40e4e5"
        }
    ]
}